I am 24 years old.  At this time I
need to take health insurance
because I am fit and fine right now.
So you are saying that your
age is currently 24 years.  So should you take the policy or
not?  No, yes, people
think health insurance is a joke.   He
says, friend, fine.  Like you are saying
in today's date.  Well, a lot of people are going to say that.
Govind Sir, I am 24 years old.  At this time
I need to take health insurance
because I am fit and
fine right now.  Well,
what do you do?  I am working now.  I do a private
job.  Yes sir.  Ok.  So you are saying
that your age is currently 24 years.  Ok.
So should you take the policy or not
?  No yes.  Because look
what happens in today's date?  Basically what happens at this age is that
people consider health insurance
a joke.  They say, friend, I am
fit and fine.  Like you are saying,
many people are going to say the same thing today.  So let me
tell you a story.   I know
one thing, I am telling you a story.  An
incident that has happened.  Right?  Now there is a guy
whose name is Rohit.  Ok?  Now
what did Rohit do?  Basically his age is almost
bigger than yours.  I am 27 years old.
Ok?  Now what has happened is that Rohit is
working in a good company.  It's fine now.  You are
young brother, 27 years old.  Ok.  I am
fond of buying new mobile phones, new laptops
, new bikes.
Ok?  What does Rohit do now?
He is spending money on all these things.  Now
his friends were saying, brother,
you should get a health insurance.
And whenever he hears about health insurance,
he keeps laughing.  Are you saying, is
health insurance a joke?  I'm fit.  Like you are
saying today you are fit.  Ok?  So he is
also saying, brother, I am fit.
Why do I need health insurance?
Ok.  I don't want health insurance.
Brother, I will buy a mobile phone, it is Apple's
15 series, right?  After that 16 will come and
then 17 in the same way as today he is
living a good lifestyle.  So he is ignoring this thing.
Correct?  Now the
friends he had with him were smart.  He, you
mean three or four more were his friends, so
they already had insurance,
medical insurance, okay, now what happened inside is
that all of them together were
very fond of travelling, so they took the car and went for a
trip, let's go and
visit some nearby place, now what happened was that while
returning from the trip, a big
accident happened
with Rohit, okay a very big accident happened,
now when the accident happened, he was taken to the hospital,
after taking him there, where there was a fracture, the doctor
said brother, you will have to undergo surgery.
Ok?  Now do you know
how much the surgery costs?  The surgery costs approximately ₹45 lakh.
Now Rohit Bhai Saheb did
not have that much savings.  He used to spend whatever money he got.
Ok?  There will be some savings.  Now
if there was a medical claim policy, then all the
claims would have been met from that.  He is brother.
Ok.  Now he had to sell his
good mobile phone.  I had to
sell the laptop as well.
Plus, what happened was that I had to
borrow money from my friends.  So now let
me tell you about Rohit's position,
where did this position reach from here?  Came down.  It went
down.  He had to sell everything.  Had to
sell it.  And I had to take a loan also.
Brother, you can borrow a life on loan
in today's date.  Isn't it?  It is a matter of shame
brother that you borrowed it from someone.  So
what happened to the lifestyle?  Came down.  Coming down to the question, if you had
paid just ₹5 or ₹100 instead of ₹45 lakh, you could have got a good health insurance today.   Do you
understand Hans Health Insurance?
Yes sir.  Yes sir.  What do you have to do first
?  You have to take a health insurance
policy.
Suppose you took a health insurance policy of ₹100 and
you got a health insurance policy of ₹5 lakh, then
think that ₹5 lakh is your bank
FD.  Ok?  Do you understand?  Only if you think like this, you will be
able to take a health insurance policy and use it
in the future.
What do people do nowadays?  The car is worth Rs 5-6
lakh.  For that, a premium of ₹15,000 is
paid so that nothing happens to the vehicle.  Isn't it
?  The car was stolen.  Ok?   I did
n't notice anything in the car, brother.  The car met with an
accident.  Lets do it.  Isn't it?  So
since the money is not spent.  Hey, you have such a great
human body.
Your human life is worth lakhs and crores of rupees.  Isn't it?
So for this, friend, is ₹5 or ₹100 a big deal
?  Isn't it?  Not there.  Not at all.
So you understood?
What does health insurance cover?  What does a medical
emergency do? It can turn a rich person into a
pauper. So, now that you
understand, you should get a policy, you should
definitely get one. That's why,
brother, if your company is
n't covering you today, if you do
n't have a health insurance policy, then
contact your insurance agent today. You should
definitely get a health insurance policy.
Even if you reduce your luxury items a little bit, you have a
budget, make a
health insurance policy in that way. If you're
procrastinating, brother, a medical emergency can
come at any time. You shouldn't tell anyone,
you should just assume you want to get a policy. You're
thinking, you're hesitating, you're
searching online, you'll say, "I'll come tomorrow, I'll come the day after tomorrow,"
no, it can
come at any time. So, when should you get a policy? Right now, at a
starting age. If you've
thought about it, you should get it now. If you want to get a
policy, contact your agent.
If you can't decide, the agent is
n't listening to you, then contact us.
Contact us on our WhatsApp number, our team will
provide you the best health insurance, ok, it is a
very good service.
We provide policy servicing on a complete all India level basis.
Provides claim service.
Plus, even abroad, like our
clients in Dubai, who are of Indian
origin, you can take a policy from there also if you want.  Even
if you are sitting there, you can still
take the policy.  So you contact us.
We will provide guidance from the best of the best.
So when should one take the policy?  You should take it now.  I
need it right now.  Right?  So this is also an
example.  The more examples you have, the more likely
you are to face such a problem.  Isn't it
?  You have to take a policy before it happens.  Isn't it
?  After this you will
not get the policy.  Will not get it.  Okay, right?  Okay, did
you understand?  Ok friends, this is
me Govinda Roy, I have been
working in this profession for more than 15 years.  And
you have settled the claims of many people.
We are serving the people today.
Right, if you have any issue, any
problem, please WhatsApp us.
Many videos on Mediclaim, Health
Insurance, Life Insurance, Mutual
Funds are available on our channel.  You can go and check it
out.  You too will see that many
videos are available on YouTube, brother.  Ok
?  OK sir.  You can go and see them too.   You
can acquire knowledge.  Rest you can get knowledge from me.
Right and the rest
we decide to give in your policy.  Ok
friends.  Sir.  See you in the next video, till then
bye Jai Hind Vande
Mataram.  Ok.